LinkedIn GitHub Portfolio Email: kyjerry0424@gmail.com

# Software Engineer at New York City, New York | No sponsorship needed

Full-stack developer with experience and passion in creating dynamic and responsive web applications. Previous background in Data Analysis with experience using Selenium for Python for web crawlers on various dynamic websites. Bilingual in English and Chinese

## **TECHNICAL & INTERPERSONAL SKILLS**

Languages: JavaScript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, SASS(SCSS), Python, JSON, EJS

Libraries and Frameworks: Node.js, React, Express.js, Mongoose, Sequelize, Jquery, Bootstrap

Databases and others: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, MySQL, RESTful Routing Interpersonal skills: Collaborative, team work, creative, Aggressive Learning

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

## Racroom - GitHub | App - React | Express.js | Node.js | MongoDB | JavaScript | JWT

An full-stack app where users can create or take trivia (in collaboration with three other engineers)

- Developed the Front-end interface with React to enable users to customize trivias with multiple quizzes with styled-components
- Designed the Front-end based on React and communicate with a MEN Stack Back-end application via AJAX with data in a MongoDB database
- Built the Back-end server that allows users with JWT authentication to perform CRUD data operations

# Joy Toy - GitHub | App - React | Express.js | Node.js | PostgreSQL | TypeScript | JavaScript | JWT

An full-stack app where users can share the toys and collections

- Developed the Front-end interface with React in Typescript that communicate with PEN Stack Back-end application with persistent data in a PostgreSQL database
- Implemented JWT token-based authorization that restricts access to features requiring a logged-in user to work (typically CUD data operations) by protecting those routes from anonymous users
- Utilized Cloudinary API that allows users to store photos of toys/collections

## Next Tour - GitHub | App - Node.js | Express.js | Mongoose | JavaScript | EJS

An MEN-stack app where users can share their trip and experience

- Created secure login with Google OAuth for authorized users to operate CUD functionalities
- Made RESTful API fetch posts and comments from the MEN Stack server and used EJS templates to render views
- Enabled users to post a trip plan that allows other users to comment and save to their page and subscribe the author

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## CLASSOVER INC - Manhattan, New York

#### **Data Operations Analyst Intern**

November 2022 - February 2023

- Developed expertise in Navicat to create detailed queries related to student, teacher, class, and attendance data in order to perform in-depth analysis and provide valuable insights
- Conducted thorough verification of MySQL queries in course and user System to ensure their accuracy and reliability
- Applied advanced web scraping techniques to effectively extract and organize critical information about prospective clients for future contact and relationship building

## CAPTARGET, LLC - (Remote) California, U.S.A

## Data Analyst Intern

March 2021 – October 2021

- Utilized advanced web scraping and automation techniques with Selenium and Python to collect and organize relevant data for client project needs and seamlessly exported it to Excel files for ease of use and analysis
- Extracted and stored information on over 500+ potential buyers of venture and capital using Selenium, Python for future decision-making and planning

## **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

JPMorgan Chase & Co. Software Engineering Virtual Experience Program on Forage (~ 5 hours)

June 2023

Completed tasks including interfacing stock price trends, creating strategies and data visualization by using Typescript, React and

**CISCO** Software Engineering Virtual Experience Program on Forage (~ 5 hours)

June 2023

Completed tasks including creation of dashboard, Sextant with React to display data, and Network Service

#### **EDUCATION**

**General Assembly** 

New York City, New York

Fairfax, Virginia

Software Engineering Immersive **George Mason University** 

January 2019-December 2020

Master of Science in Data Analytics Engineering, GPA:3.87/4.0 **National Taiwan Ocean University** Keelung, Taiwan September 2011-June 2015

Bachelor of Science in System Engineering & Naval Architecture